{
    "id": "b7bb381aae3e412ebd60095c2e94e9bb",
    "title": "Two word verbs exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "555b3c6598d9491596e268d9f6f758e1",
            "title": "Two Word Verbs Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "The politician broke ———————– in the middle of his speech.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "up",
                        "down",
                        "up",
                        "in"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Could you blow —————– the candle?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "up",
                        "off",
                        "out"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "At last the storm has blown —————-",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "over",
                        "off",
                        "out"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The opposition parties said that they would bring ————– a No-Confidence Motion against the Prime Minister.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "up",
                        "forward",
                        "out",
                        "about"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The witness said that she could not call ————— the whole events.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "up",
                        "out",
                        "on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The labour union leaders have called —————- the strike.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "on",
                        "off",
                        "at",
                        "in"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The investigating officer tried to call —————- vital information from the accused.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "up",
                        "forth",
                        "out",
                        "in"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The army foiled the terrorists’ plan to blow ——————— the bridge.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "over",
                        "up",
                        "out"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He is cut —————- for a career in sales and marketing.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "in",
                        "out",
                        "up"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "If you work hard, you will come ——————- with flying colors in the examination.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "out",
                        "off",
                        "up"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}